<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>

    <string name="app_name">Slider Menu</string>
    <string name="action_logout">Logout</string>
    <string name="action_help">Help</string>
    <string name="hello_world">Hello world!</string>
    <string name="drawer_open">Slider Menu Opened</string>
    <string name="drawer_close">Slider Menu Closed</string>


    <string name="university_text">Y S Institute of Engineering and Technology is one of the oldest
        college affiliated to Dream Technical University, India and is approved by AICTE.
        Since then it has been marching on with focus on exploring and creating new avenues for young
        aspirants through collaborations with Institutions and Industries of National and International repute.</string>

    <string name="admission_text">One can directly apply for Management Seats by filling up the forms available at Admission Offices.
        The selection would be thoroughly based on merit basis. The applicants would have to go through an interview conducted by Admission Board.
        The members of this Admission Board are higher dignitaries from various Departments of the group.
        For applying for Counselling Seats one needs to appear in the Appropriate Entrance Exam for the Specific Course.
        The counselling Seat would be allotted as per the University Norms.</string>

    <string name="placements_text">Y S institute is having highly dedicated and fully independent career development and placement facilitation services
        cell operating under the direct control of management of the Group.
        The cell is headed by Director - CRC and PFC and has independent staff consisting of TPOs faculty and students placement coordinators drawn from various departments of YS.
        For placement a large number of prospective employers are contacted during the year and efforts are made to invite these companies to visit college and to conduct campus recruitments.</string>

    <string name="faculties_text">YS Institute has ones of the best state of art laboratories which are self contained and matching with the Industry Standards.
        Mechanical Labs are equipped with the - Engg. Workshop Practice Lab, Mechanics of Solids Lab Thermal Engg. Lab, Metrology Lab,
        FM  HMS Lab, Production Technology Lab, Metrology  M/C Tools Lab, Heat Transfer Lab, CAD/CAM Lab and Fuel  Lubricant Lab etc.</string>

    <string name="support_text">Slider Menu Closed</string>

    <string name="help_text">Made By Yasham Singhal
                                Version 1.0
                            Stay Tuned for more exciting stuff.
    </string>

    <!-- Nav Drawer Menu Items -->
    <string-array name="nav_drawer_items">
        <item >Home</item>
        <item >Admissions</item>
        <item >Faculties</item>
        <item >Placements</item>
        <item >Contact Us</item>
     </string-array>
    
    <!-- Nav Drawer List Item Icons -->
    <!-- Keep them in order as the titles are in -->
    <array name="nav_drawer_icons">
        <item>@mipmap/ic_universityhome</item>
        <item>@mipmap/ic_admission</item>
        <item>@mipmap/ic_faculties</item>
        <item>@mipmap/ic_placements</item>
        <item>@mipmap/ic_support</item>
    </array>
    
    <!-- Content Description -->
    <string name="desc_list_item_icon">Item Icon</string>

</resources>
